Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files K-O, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files M
    - Mayhawk, Robert (Box A-80, Folder 264)
    - Mayhew, Alice (Box A-80, Folder 265)
    - Mayhew, Richard (Box A-80, Folder 266)
    - Mayher, Robt. (Box A-80, Folder 267)
    - Maymi, Carmen (Box A-80, Folder 268)
    - Dr. Maynard, Aubre (Box A-80, Folder 269)
      Photographer if identified: Dr. K. Meyerowitz,
    - Maynard, Cathy (Box A-80, Folder 270)
    - Maynard, Clement T. (Box A-80, Folder 271)
      Photographer if identified: Fred Maura,
    - Maynard, Don (Box A-80, Folder 272)
    - Maynard, Gloria (Box A-80, Folder 273)
    - Maynard, Godfrey E. (Capt.) (Box A-80, Folder 274)
    - Maynard, Herbert (Rev.) (Box A-80, Folder 275)
    - Maynard, Joan A. (Box A-80, Folder 276)
      Also 1 photocopy.
    - Maynard, Joseph A., IV (Mrs.) (Box A-80, Folder 277)
    - Maynard, Kathleen S. (Box A-80, Folder 278)
    - Maynard, Mujaahid (Box A-80, Folder 279)
    - Maynard, Joan (Box A-80, Folder 280)
    - Mayne, Harris V. (Box A-80, Folder 281)
    - Maynard, Roy E. (Box A-80, Folder 282)
    - Maynard, Valerie (Box A-80, Folder 283)
    - Maynard, Winston A. (Box A-80, Folder 284)
    - Maynor, Dorothy (Box A-81, Folder 1)
      Also one velox print, press releases.
      Photographer if identified: David McAdams, Mike Zwerling,
    - Maynor, Reggie (Box A-81, Folder 2)
    - Mayo, Andree (Box A-81, Folder 3)
    - Mayo, Barry (Box A-81, Folder 4)
    - Mayo, Charles C. (Box A-81, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Photokraft, US Army
    - Mayo, Harry (Pvt.) (Box A-81, Folder 6)
      Photographer if identified: US Air Force
    - Mayo, James E. (Box A-81, Folder 7)
    - Spencer Mayo (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 8)
    - Mayo, Spencer (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 9)
    - Mayo, Steve (Box A-81, Folder 10)
    - Mayo, Whitman (Box A-81, Folder 11)
      Photographer if identified: Guy Crowder,
    - Mayo, William H. Jr. (Box A-81, Folder 12)
    - Mayors (Box A-81, Folder 13)
    - Mayrant, David (Box A-81, Folder 14)
    - Mays, Billie (Box A-81, Folder 15)
    - Mays, Charles E. (Box A-81, Folder 16)
    - Mays, Charlie (Box A-81, Folder 17)
    - Mays, Dale L. (Box A-81, Folder 18)
    - Mays, Ella K. (Box A-81, Folder 19)
      Photographer if identified: John E. Freed
    - Mays, Geneva (Box A-81, Folder 20)
    - Mays, Mr. & Mrs. Joseph (Rowena) (Box A-81, Folder 21)
    - Mays, Leonora (Box A-81, Folder 22)
    - Mays, Marghuerite (Mrs. Willie) (Box A-81, Folder 23)
      Also newspaper clipping. 3 prints have newspaper clipping taped to verso. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Harris Photo, M Associates
    - Mays, Michael (Box A-81, Folder 24)
    - Mays, Nebraska Dr. (Box A-81, Folder 25)
    - Mays, Rowena (Box A-81, Folder 26)
      Also one velox print and an invitation to Rowena's showing 9-16-1962.
    - Mays, William (Box A-81, Folder 27)
      Photographer if identified: Hayes/L.I.P.P.A.
    - Mays, Willie (Box A-81, Folder 28)
      1 print mounted on cardboard.
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Carl Nesfield/NYC Photo Service, Hale Haberman, James C. Campbell, Layne's Studio, TWA, International News Photos, American Airlines
    - Mays, Willie (Box A-81, Folder 29)
      Also 3 velox prints, one paper stereotype matrix, and several newspaper clippings. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: United Press International, Wide World Photos, Harris Photo, US Army, Robert Johnson/Freelance East, James Gilbert
    - Mays, Willie (Box A-81, Folder 30)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Price, Bill Mitchell, Harris Photo
    - Mays, Willmia (Box A-81, Folder 31)
    - Mayson, Irene Mrs. (Box A-81, Folder 32)
    - Maze (Box A-81, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: Todd Gray, Barbara DuMetz, Craig Kolb
    - Mazen, Aaron (Box A-81, Folder 34)
    - Mazuri, Ali Dr. (Box A-81, Folder 35)
    - Mazzilli, Lee (Box A-81, Folder 36)
    - Mbadiwe, K. O. (Box A-81, Folder 37)
      1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Pan American World Airways,
    - Mbali, Sophie (Box A-81, Folder 38)
      Photographer if identified: Press and Information Department Sabena
    - Mberi, Antar (Box A-81, Folder 39)
    - Mbirika, Abukuse (Box A-81, Folder 40)
      Photographer if identified: Multipics Studios,
    - Mbiti, John S. Prof. (Box A-81, Folder 41)
    - Mboya, Catherine (Box A-81, Folder 42)
    - Mboya, Tom (Box A-81, Folder 43)
      Photographer if identified: David J. M. Robinson, Bro. David McAdams, Wide World Photos
    - Mboyo, Paul (Box A-81, Folder 44)
    - Mbuinga, Landula (Box A-81, Folder 45)
    - Mbulo, Letta (Box A-81, Folder 46)
    - Mbwuike, Ulum (Box A-81, Folder 47)
    - MC Lyte (Velox) (Box A-81, Folder 48)
    - McAdams, Robert (Box A-81, Folder 49)
    - McAdoo, Bob (Box A-81, Folder 50)
    - McAllister, Al (Box A-81, Folder 51)
    - McAllister, Elizabeth (Box A-81, Folder 52)
    - McAllister, Normajean (Box A-81, Folder 53)
    - McAlpin, Harry S. (Box A-81, Folder 54)
    - McAndrew, J. (Box A-81, Folder 55)
    - McAndrew, Marianne (Box A-81, Folder 56)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (General) (Box A-81, Folder 57)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix, envelope of negatives. 1 print mounted on matte. 1 print mounted on cardboard.
      Photographer if identified: Signal Corps Photo, L. St. Clair Dummett
    - MacArthur Parade - Dummett (Box A-81, Folder 57)
      Dated 4-20-1951. 3 strips and 1 loose frame, 6"x6" negatives. 9 images.
    - MacArthur, Mrs. Douglas (Box A-81, Folder 58)
    - McArthur, Samuel (Box A-81, Folder 59)
    - McAshan, Eddie (Box A-81, Folder 60)
    - McAshan, Eugene E. Rev. (Box A-81, Folder 61)
    - McAssey, Mary (Box A-81, Folder 62)
    - McBarnett, Bruce (Box A-81, Folder 63)
    - McBarnette, Lorna (Box A-81, Folder 64)
    - McBarnette, Olvin (Box A-81, Folder 65)
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett, Harris Photo
    - McBean, Al (Box A-81, Folder 66)
    - McBee, Richard (Box A-81, Folder 67)
    - McBride, Archie (Box A-81, Folder 68)
      Photographer if identified: Lufthansa
    - McBride, Cornell (Box A-81, Folder 69)
    - McBride, David (Box A-81, Folder 70)
      Photographer if identified: Office of Public Information, Denison University
    - McBride, Ken "Strike" (Box A-81, Folder 71)
    - McBride, Lisa (Box A-81, Folder 72)
    - McBride, Lola (Box A-81, Folder 73)
    - McBride, Richard (Box A-81, Folder 74)
    - McBride, Rose Marie (Box A-81, Folder 75)
    - McBroom, Marcia (Box A-81, Folder 76)
      Also 3 velox prints, 1 promotional postcard.
      Photographer if identified: Maury Englander,
    - McBroom, Marcia (Box A-81, Folder 77)
    - McBroom, Marie Lee (Box A-81, Folder 78)
    - McBrown, Gertrude (Box A-81, Folder 79)
    - MacBryde, Leo (Box A-81, Folder 80)
    - McBurrows, Theodius (Box A-81, Folder 81)
      Photographer if identified: Consolidated News Pictures
    - McCabe, Edward J. (Box A-81, Folder 82)
    - Eugene McCabe (Box A-81, Folder 83)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, Curt Clemons,
    - Jewell McCabe (Box A-81, Folder 84)
    - McCabe, Jewell J. (Box A-81, Folder 85)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, NYS Department of Commerce
    - McCaden, Margaret also McBroom, Marcia (Box A-81, Folder 86)
    - McCaffrey, Bernard (Box A-81, Folder 87)
    - McCaffrey, Mildred Mrs. (Box A-81, Folder 88)
    - McCaffrey, Gen. Wm. F. (Box A-81, Folder 89)
    - McCain, Anna (Box A-81, Folder 90)
    - McCain, Bernie (Box A-81, Folder 91)
      Photographer if identified: Photograph by Jeb
    - McCain, Bernie R. (Box A-81, Folder 92)
    - McCain, Earl (Box A-81, Folder 93)
      Photographer if identified: Herber Gould
    - McCain, Les (Box A-81, Folder 94)
    - McCain, Mel (Box A-81, Folder 95)
    - McCain, Mitchell A. (Box A-81, Folder 96)
    - McCain, Shirley (Box A-81, Folder 97)
    - McCain, W. Calvin (Box A-81, Folder 98)
    - McClain, Janice (Box A-81, Folder 99)
    - McClain, Saundra (Box A-81, Folder 100)
    - McCall, Alvin (Box A-81, Folder 101)
    - McCall, Barry (Box A-81, Folder 102)
    - H. Carl McCall (Box A-81, Folder 103)
    - Carl McCall (Box A-81, Folder 104)
      Also 1 newspaper clipping. One print has staple through edge. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan, Bill Moore, Pictorial Enterprise, James Gilbert
    - McCall, Celia (Box A-81, Folder 105)
    - McCall, Charles (Box A-81, Folder 106)
    - McCall, David B. (Box A-81, Folder 107)
    - Esther McCall (Box A-81, Folder 108)
    - McCall, Esther (Box A-81, Folder 109)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Pictorial Enterprise
    - McCall, Ida (Box A-81, Folder 110)
    - McCall, Marty (Box A-81, Folder 111)
    - McCall, Wm. R. (Box A-81, Folder 112)
    - McCalla, Nathan (Box A-81, Folder 113)
    - McCallum, Linda (Box A-81, Folder 114)
    - McCann, Francis (Box A-81, Folder 115)
    - McCann, Gerald (Box A-81, Folder 116)
      Polaroid print, taped to recto of typescript leaf.
    - McCann, Les (Box A-81, Folder 117)
    - McCann, Lucy (Box A-81, Folder 118)
    - McCann, Thomas (Box A-81, Folder 119)
    - McCant, William (Box A-81, Folder 120)
    - McCants, Dorry (Box A-81, Folder 121)
    - McCants, Frank (Box A-81, Folder 122)
    - McCants, Greg (Box A-81, Folder 123)
    - McCants, Rev. Gregory (Box A-81, Folder 124)
    - McCants, Iris (Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 125)
    - McCants, Julia (Box A-81, Folder 126)
    - McCants, Reed (Box A-81, Folder 127)
    - Reed "Live" McCants (Box A-81, Folder 128)
    - McCants, Robert (Box A-81, Folder 129)
    - McCants, Solomon D. (Box A-81, Folder 130)
    - McCarden, Carl (Box A-81, Folder 131)
    - McCarroll, Jesse (Box A-81, Folder 132)
    - McCarther, Avis (Box A-81, Folder 133)
    - McCarthy, Charles E. (Box A-81, Folder 134)
      Photographer if identified: NYCPD
    - McCarthy, Dave (Box A-81, Folder 135)
    - McCarthy, Eugene Senator (Box A-81, Folder 136)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, Harris Photo, Monroe S. Frederick II, Alan Tepper
    - McCarthy, Eugene Mrs. (Box A-81, Folder 137)
    - McCarthy, Henry L. (Box A-81, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: The Welfarer, Timothey Buckley
    - McCarthy, James E. Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-81, Folder 139)
    - McCarthy, Kevin (Box A-81, Folder 140)
    - McCarthy, Lucille S. (Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 141)
      Photographer if identified: Kurt Brunson
    - McCarthy, Oceola (Box A-81, Folder 142)
    - McCarthy, Richard (Box A-81, Folder 143)
    - McCarthy, Thomas P. / Karen McClennan (Box A-81, Folder 144)
      Photographer if identified: Yorkville Photo Studio,
    - McCarthy, William (Box A-81, Folder 145)
    - McCartney, Torrie (Box A-81, Folder 146)
    - Torrie McCartney (Box A-81, Folder 147)
    - McCartrey, Doris (Box A-81, Folder 148)
    - McCarty, Oseola (Box A-81, Folder 149)
    - Macaulay, Josephine (Box A-81, Folder 150)
    - McCauley, William E. (Box A-81, Folder 151)
    - McCaw, Arthur B. (Box A-81, Folder 152)
    - McCaw, Valaria Lee (Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 153)
      Also envelope, press release.
      Photographer if identified: Agency for International Development
    - McClain, Delphina (Box A-81, Folder 154)
    - McClain, Genevieve (Box A-81, Folder 155)
    - McClain, Lonnie (Box A-81, Folder 165)
    - McClain, Milton (Box A-81, Folder 166)
      Photographer if identified: Russ Carter Studio
    - McClain, Sandy (Box A-81, Folder 167)
    - McClain, Thomas A. (Box A-81, Folder 168)
    - McClammy, James (Box A-81, Folder 169)
    - McClane, Curtis (Box A-81, Folder 170)
      Photographer if identified: James C. Campbell, B. Grant,
    - McClane, Kenneth A. Dr. & Junior (Box A-81, Folder 171)
      Photographer if identified: Photokraft, M. Smith,
    - McClane, Dr. & Mrs. Kenneth A. (Box A-81, Folder 172)
      Photographer if identified: Photokraft, Bro. David McAdams, Nichols, James C. Campbell
    - McClane, Lorenzo & Henrietta (Box A-81, Folder 173)
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett, Helen Merrill
    - Lorenzo McClane 25 Anniversary - Dummett (Box A-81, Folder 173)
      Dated 6-20-1948. 1 strip of 6"x6" negatives. 2 images.
    - McClane, Roberta (Box A-81, Folder 174)
    - McClane, Walter (Box A-81, Folder 175)
    - McClaney, Eula (Box A-81, Folder 176)
    - McClaney, Eula (Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 177)
    - McClenny, T. B. (Box A-81, Folder 178)
    - McClare, Claude (Box A-81, Folder 179)
    - McClarrin, Otto (Box A-81, Folder 180)
    - McClarrin, Vaughn Otto (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 181)
      Photographer if identified: U.S.A.A.F., Scurlock
    - McClean, Violet (Box A-81, Folder 182)
    - McClellan, Mike (Box A-81, Folder 183)
    - McClelland, Jerona (Box A-81, Folder 184)
    - McClelland, Mel (Box A-81, Folder 185)
      1 print is of John McCurry. 1 print has ms. caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Boris Bakchy, James J. Kriegsmann, Cecil Layne
    - McClellon, William (Box A-81, Folder 186)
    - McClendon, Catherine Mrs. (Box A-81, Folder 187)
      Photographer if identified: Board of Education, NYC
    - McClendon, Ernestine (Box A-81, Folder 188)
    - McClendon, Grace (Box A-81, Folder 189)
      Photographer if identified: James T. Higdon
    - McClendon, James Rev. (Box A-81, Folder 190)
    - Raymond McClendon (Box A-81, Folder 191)
    - McClendon, Thomas G. (Box A-81, Folder 192)
    - McClennan, Henry L. (Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 193)
    - McClenney, Cheryl Ilene (Box A-81, Folder 194)
    - McClenney, Clifton (Box A-81, Folder 195)
      Print mounted on cardboard and has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    - McClenney, E. H. (Dr.) (Box A-81, Folder 196)
    - McClennon, Eleanor (Box A-81, Folder 197)
    - McClintock, Ernie (Box A-81, Folder 198)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Greene
    - McClinton, Curtis (Box A-81, Folder 199)
      Photographer if identified: Laughead
    - McClinton, O. B. (Box A-81, Folder 200)
    - McCloud, Dorothy (Box A-81, Folder 201)
      Photographer if identified: Mallory, Bro. David McAdams
    - McCloud, J. Oscar Rev. (Box A-81, Folder 202)
    - McCloud, Mack (Box A-81, Folder 203)
    - McCloud, Sharon (Box A-81, Folder 204)
    - McCloud, Theodore (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 205)
    - McClung, Thelma (Box A-81, Folder 206)
    - McClure, Cameron Mr. (Box A-81, Folder 207)
    - McClure, Doug (Box A-81, Folder 208)
    - McClure, Willie (Box A-81, Folder 209)
    - McClurkin, W. D. (Box A-81, Folder 210)
    - McCluskey, John A. (Box A-81, Folder 211)
    - McCollough, Bob (Box A-81, Folder 212)
    - McCollough, C. Peter (Box A-81, Folder 213)
    - McCollough, Walter (Bishop) (Box A-81, Folder 214)
      Approximately 6 prints are stuck to back of folder. Two groups of prints (2 and approximately 4, respectively) are stuck together with paste. Also one contact sheet (8 images). 2 prints have typescript caption taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Chuck Smith, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - McCollough, Walter (Bishop) (Box A-81, Folder 215)
    - McCollum, John (Box A-81, Folder 216)
    - McCollum, Padgett (Box A-81, Folder 217)
    - McCollum, Ruby (Box A-81, Folder 218)
      Print mounted between 2 layers of cardboard.
    - McCombs, Carolyn (Box A-81, Folder 219)
      Print has typescript caption taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Ed Flournoy
    - McConn, Thomas (Box A-81, Folder 220)
    - McConnell, Dudley Dr. (Box A-81, Folder 221)
    - McConnell, Roland C. (Box A-81, Folder 222)
      Photographer if identified: DeWayne Wickham
    - McCoo, Marilyn & Billy Davis (Box A-81, Folder 223)
    - McCord, Arthur A. (Box A-81, Folder 224)
    - McCord, Jacqueline (Box A-81, Folder 225)
    - McCord, James Sgt. (Box A-81, Folder 226)
    - McCord, Robert (Box A-81, Folder 227)
    - McCord, Thomasine (Box A-81, Folder 228)
    - McCormack, Elizabeth J. (Box A-81, Folder 229)
    - McCormack, John (Box A-81, Folder 230)
    - McCormick, Barbara (Box A-81, Folder 231)
    - Betty McCormick (Box A-81, Folder 232)
    - McCormick, Joyce (Box A-81, Folder 233)
    - McCormick, Larry (Box A-81, Folder 234)
    - McCormick, Parker (Box A-81, Folder 235)
      Photographer if identified: Miss Alix Jeffry
    - McCormick, Rita P. (Box A-81, Folder 236)
    - McCornell, David (Box A-81, Folder 237)
      Polaroid print (coated) taped to cardboard.
    - McCottry, Kenneth & Mrs.Ellen McCottry (Box A-81, Folder 238)
    - McCovey, Willie (Box A-81, Folder 239)
    - McCown, Ira (Mrs.) (Box A-81, Folder 240)
    - McCoy, Carrie Mrs. (Box A-81, Folder 241)
    - McCoy, Edward Jr. (Box A-81, Folder 242)
      Print is in envelope.
    - McCoy, Eleanor (Box A-81, Folder 243)
    - McCoy, Henry (Box A-81, Folder 244)
    - McCoy, Jim (Box A-81, Folder 245)
    - McCoy, Leamon (Box A-81, Folder 246)
    - McCoy, Malcolm (Box A-81, Folder 247)
    - McCoy, Paula (Box A-81, Folder 248)
    - McCoy, Pete (Box A-81, Folder 249)
      Photographer if identified: Everett Reese
    - McCoy, Rhody A. (Box A-81, Folder 250)
      Also 2 velox prints. 4 prints have a staple. 2 groups of 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, Ace Creative Photos, James Gilbert, King Photographers, Pictorial Enterprise, Tex Harris, Hamilton Associates
    - McCoy, Seth (Box A-81, Folder 251)
    - McCoy, Sid (Box A-81, Folder 252)
    - McCoy, Steve (Box A-81, Folder 253)
    - McCoy, Van (Box A-81, Folder 254)
    - Van McCoy (Box A-81, Folder 255)
    - McCracken, James (Box A-81, Folder 256)
    - McCracken. Paul W. (Box A-81, Folder 257)
    - McCrae, Carmen (Box A-81, Folder 258)
    - McCrae, Genera Mrs. (Box A-81, Folder 259)
    - McCrae, George & Gwen (Box A-81, Folder 260)
    - McCrae, Gwen (Box A-81, Folder 261)
    - McCrae, Rudolph (Box A-81, Folder 262)
    - McCracken, Renee (Box A-81, Folder 263)
    - McCraley, Robert Fr. (Box A-81, Folder 264)
      Photographer if identified: Layne Photo, A. Hansen Studio
    - McCraney, Bryant (Box A-81, Folder 265)
    - Bill McCrary (Box A-81, Folder 266)
    - McCrary, Lisa (Box A-81, Folder 267)
    - McCrary, Michelle (Box A-81, Folder 268)
    - McCrary, Tex (Box A-81, Folder 269)
    - McCraw, Tom (Box A-81, Folder 270)
    - McCray, Andrew (Box A-81, Folder 271)
    - McCray, Margaret (Box A-81, Folder 272)
    - McCray, Nona (Box A-81, Folder 273)
    - McCray, Robert (Box A-81, Folder 274)
    - McCray, Thelma (Box A-81, Folder 275)
    - McCray, Walter (Box A-81, Folder 276)
    - McCreary, Bill (Box A-81, Folder 277)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Office of Public Information, Jamaica
    - Bill McCreary (Box A-81, Folder 278)
    - McCreary, Edward (Box A-81, Folder 279)
    - McCreary, Pete (Box A-81, Folder 280)
    - McCreary, Margy B. (Box A-81, Folder 281)
    - McCree, Ethel A. (Box A-81, Folder 282)
      Photographer if identified: Jim Curry Associates
    - McCree, Floyd J. (Box A-81, Folder 283)
    - McCree, Fred (Box A-81, Folder 284)
    - McCree, Wade Jr. (Box A-81, Folder 285)
    - McCreedy Mr. Ward See Carrie Edgar (Box A-81, Folder 286)
    - McCrey, Maxine (Box A-81, Folder 287)
    - McCrimons, Daniel (Box A-81, Folder 288)
    - McCrum, Lloyd D. (Box A-81, Folder 289)
    - McCullen, Melody (Box A-81, Folder 290)
      Photographer if identified: Job Corps
    - McCullen, Michael Mrs. (Box A-81, Folder 291)
    - McCuller, Bishop (Box A-81, Folder 292)
    - McCollom, Padgette (Box A-81, Folder 293)
    - McCullouch, Earl (Box A-81, Folder 294)
    - McCullough, Betty Ann (Box A-81, Folder 295)
    - McCullough, Bob (Box A-81, Folder 296)
    - McCullough, Connie (Box A-81, Folder 297)
    - McCullough, Derrick (Box A-81, Folder 298)
    - McCullough, Margaret (Box A-81, Folder 299)
    - McCullough, Melvin (Box A-81, Folder 300)
    - McCullough, Robert (Box A-81, Folder 301)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Bob Head, L. St. Clair Dummett,
    - McCullough, Ullanda (Box A-81, Folder 302)
    - McCullum, Irving (Box A-81, Folder 303)
      Print stapled to newsprint-type paper.
    - McCurdy, Robert (Box A-81, Folder 304)
      Photographer if identified: N.Y.R.A.
    - McCurry, John (Box A-81, Folder 305)
    - McCutcheon, Lawrence (Box A-81, Folder 306)
    - Brett Maxie (Box A-81, Folder 307)
    - McDaniel, Abraham (Box A-82, Folder 1)
    - McDaniel, Adam (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-82, Folder 2)
    - McDaniel, Hattie (Box A-82, Folder 3)
    - McDaniel, Kenneth (Box A-82, Folder 4)
      Photographer if identified: Norfolk State University
    - McDaniel, Linwood (Box A-82, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Carrie Boretz
    - McDaniel, Lorene (Box A-82, Folder 6)
      Photographer if identified: David A. McLintock
    - McDaniel, Myra (Box A-82, Folder 7)
    - McDaniel, Robert O. (Box A-82, Folder 8)
    - McDaniels, Desiree (Box A-82, Folder 9)
    - McDaniels, Elder (Box A-82, Folder 10)
    - McDaniels, Gene (Box A-82, Folder 11)
    - McDaniels, Herman (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-82, Folder 12)
    - McDaniels, Jim (Box A-82, Folder 13)
    - McDaniels, Lathia (Box A-82, Folder 14)
    - McDaniels, Robert (Box A-82, Folder 15)
    - McDavid, Felix (Box A-82, Folder 16)
    - McDearmon, Harrold (Box A-82, Folder 17)
    - McDonald, Beatrice (Mrs.) (Box A-82, Folder 18)
    - McDonald, Bernard (Box A-82, Folder 19)
      Photographer if identified: Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation
    - MacDonald, Byrnes (Box A-82, Folder 20)
    - McDonald, Carol (Box A-82, Folder 21)
      Print is torn and repaired with tape on the verso.
    - McDonald, Charles (Box A-82, Folder 22)
    - McDonald, Charles (Box A-82, Folder 23)
    - McDonald, Country Joe (Box A-82, Folder 24)
    - McDonald, Edna (Ms.) (Box A-82, Folder 25)
      Photographer if identified: University News Bureau/Temple University
    - McDonald, Ella S. (Box A-82, Folder 26)
    - McDonald, Ernest (Dr.) (Box A-82, Folder 27)
      Also one black and white 6"x6" negative frame in an envelope.
    - McDonald, Frank, Jr. (Box A-82, Folder 28)
      Print in small envelope.
    - McDonald, George D. (Box A-82, Folder 29)
    - MacDonald, Gladys (see Pauline J. Williams) (Box A-82, Folder 30)
      Photographer if identified: Photokraft, M & M Smith
    - MacDonald, Hilda (Box A-82, Folder 31)
      Also one strip black and white 6"x6" negatives, two frames, in an envelope.
      Photographer if identified: Nichols, James Campbell, Bro. David McAdams
    - McDonald, Iris (Box A-82, Folder 32)
    - McDonald, James (Box A-82, Folder 33)
    - McDonald, Jesse (Box A-82, Folder 34)
    - MacDonald, Jeanette (Box A-82, Folder 35)
    - McDonald, Jimmy (Box A-82, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: WHYY/Philadelphia
    - McDonald, Lillian (Miss) (Box A-82, Folder 37)
    - MacDonald, Miles (Box A-82, Folder 38)
    - McDonald, Parker (Box A-82, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: Herald Sports
    - McDonald, Patsy L. (Box A-82, Folder 40)
    - McDonald, Ralph (Box A-82, Folder 41)
      Also one cut-out rubylith film. Also one velox print.
    - McDonald, Ralph (Box A-82, Folder 42)
    - McDonald, Ron (Box A-82, Folder 43)
      Photographer if identified: Billie Billing
    - McDonald, Roslyn (Box A-82, Folder 44)
      Photographer if identified: Frumkin Studio
    - McDonald, Roslyn G. (Box A-82, Folder 45)
      Also one three-leaf typescript release paperclipped to a print.
    - MacDonald, Ruth (Box A-82, Folder 46)
    - McDonald, William (Box A-82, Folder 47)